net.com 2014-11-28

# Privacy Policy | Sonus

Sonus is committed to preserving your right to privacy when you visit us on the Web. In general, you can visit our website without revealing any information about yourself or your company.

## What information do we collect?

There are some sections of our site that invite you to contact us for more information, in which case we may request your name and email address or other personal information. Some of the reasons we may request your personal information include:

  * To permit you to register for an account;
  * To permit you to request information about us or our products;
  * To permit you to request service and support for our products or to permit us to provide you such support; and
  * To permit you to apply for a job at Sonus.

If you give us your personal information, we will inform you how we will use it. Your personal information will only be used in the ways specified when it is collected.

The information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience – your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs;
  * To provide support and assistance for our products;
  * To improve our website – we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you;
  * To improve customer service – your information helps us to respond more effectively to your customer service requests and support needs; and
  * To send periodic emails or contact you by other means (Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email).

We track the domains from which our visitors come to collect statistics on our site traffic for usage and trend analysis; however, we do not link your Internet address to anything identifiable to you as an individual.

## Cookies

Sonus's website utilizes "cookies." Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow it) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for marketing purposes unless you have granted us permission to do so. We may, however, share your personal information within Sonus and its subsidiaries for purposes of data processing or storage. We may also respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process by disclosing your personal information and other related information, if required to do so. We may collect and share your personal information and any other information available to us in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Sonus's terms of use or as otherwise required by law.

## Third party links

Occasionally, we may include or offer links to third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies, and we have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and our reputation and welcome any negative feedback about these sites. Sonus encourages you to review the privacy policies posted on the sites you visit.

## California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act; we will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

## Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act). Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older and we do not intentionally collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age.

## Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

## Conditions of Use

Please also visit our Terms & Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at Terms & Conditions.

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our website's privacy policy.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

Sonus may amend this privacy policy at any time and from time to time. Your continued use of the Sonus Web site after any change will signify your consent to those changes.

This policy was last modified on May 25, 2012

## Customers

  * MathWorks estimates that through the automated provisioning and call routing features of the Sonus solution, the company has freed up more than 250 IT staff hours per week for more important projects.

MathWorks is the leading developer of mathematical computing software for engineers and scientists. Founded in 1984, MathWorks employs 2800 people in 15 countries, with headquarters in Natick, Massachusetts, U.S.A.

  * The industry-leading performance and scale of Sonus' SBC 5100 allows us to maintain a competitive edge in the market while delivering exceptional customer service. 

Smart Tel is a major player in the Singapore telecommunications industry and aims to develop its global presence with new offices in Australia, Thailand, Indonesia, Philippines, India, South Africa, the US and the UK, with cost effective, easy-to-use and scalable telephony solutions. 

  * We wanted to work with an industry-leading SBC vendor and our market analysis indicated that Sonus was the clear choice for this partnership.

(GCS) is a software company founded in 2006 by Neal Axelrad and Jay Meranchik. GCS' goal is to be the best company in the marketplace. We are privately held and have offices in New York & New Jersey USA. 

  * Sonus made the deployment, integration and migration to Microsoft Lync easy. 

We are experts in identifying and delivering flexible communication solutions that scale and adapt to your business demands, empowering your business to do more, faster and with less effort and cost.
